elitmus.com 2017-06-06

# eLitmus.com | Privacy Policy / Disclaimer

This policy was last modified on January 16, 2013 and was first published and made effective in March 2012 

**www.elitmus.com** ( hereinafter referred to as **"Website"** or **"eLitmus"** ) is a public website owned by **"eLitmus Evaluation Private Limited"**. The privacy policy sets out how **eLitmus** uses and protects any information that you give **eLitmus** when you use this website. **eLitmus** is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. **eLitmus** may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

**What we collect**  
We may collect the following information:

  * Bio-data of the user including educational qualifications and professional experience
  * Contact information including email address and telephone number
  * Identification information including photograph and signature in any form
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests.
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Profile the user
  * Internal record keeping
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes
  * We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests
  * We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Accessing and updating your personal information**  
A user can access all the data that he or she has entered during the registration process on our website. However, some of our services may require us to lock the user's personal information, and it may not be possible to edit such information once locked. Only information such as Contact number, address, alternate email etc can be updated as and when required, by accessing our website. Furthermore, if the user wants to change the locked information, he or she can do so by following the instructions mentioned in the 'help' section of our website.

**Data Retention**  
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at query@elitmus.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

However the internet is an ever evolving medium. We may change our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

**Payment Gateway Disclaimer**  
Payments by you to eLitmus may be made through an electronic and automated collection and remittance service (the “Payment Gateway”) hosted through CCAvenue (the 'Payment Service Provider'). The Payment Gateway service is provided to you in order to facilitate access to view and pay online.

**eLitmus** makes no representation of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of the Payment Gateway. You expressly agree that your use of this online payment service is entirely at your own risk.

**Limitation of Liability**

  * eLitmus has made this service available to you as a matter of convenience. eLitmus expressly disclaims any claim or liability arising out of the provision of this service. You agree and acknowledge that you shall be solely responsible for your conduct and that eLitmus reserves the right to terminate your rights to use the service immediately.
  * In no way shall eLitmus, the Payment Service Provider or its affiliates be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or exemplary damages, including but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, goodwill, data or other intangible losses arising out of or in connection with the access to, use of, or reliance on the the Payment Gateway services.
  * eLitmus and the Payment Service Provider assumes no liability whatsoever for any monetary or other damage suffered by you on account of 
    * the delay, failure, interruption, or corruption of any data or other information transmitted in connection with use of the Payment Gateway; or 
    * any interruption or errors in the operation of the Payment Gateway.
  * You shall indemnify and hold harmless eLitmus and their respective officers, directors, agents, and employees, from any claim or demand, or actions.
  * You agree, understand and confirm that personal data including without limitation, details relating to debit card/credit card transmitted over the Internet is susceptible to misuse, theft and/or fraud and that eLitmus has no control over such matters.
  * Although all reasonable care has been taken towards guarding against unauthorized use of any information transmitted by you, eLitmus does not represent or guarantee that the use of the payment gateway will not result in theft and/or unauthorized use of data over the Internet.
  * eLitmus, the Payment Service Providers and its affiliates and associates shall not be liable, at any time, for any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, communications line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, alteration of, or use of information contained in the Payment Gateway.
  * To register with this website or to use certain services and tools, you may have to create your User ID and Password. Your User ID and Password are very important pieces of information and it is your responsibility to keep them secured. You agree to; 
    * Choose a new password, whenever you required to do so.
    * Keep your User ID & Password confidential.
    * Be responsible for any transactions made by Users, you have authorized to
    * use your User ID and Password.

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. eLitmus will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your eLitmus account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet café

**Debit/Credit card details**  
The debit/credit card details provided by you for use of the Payment Gateway will be correct and accurate and you shall not use a debit/credit card, which is not lawfully owned by you. You further agree and undertake to provide correct and valid debit/credit card details.

You may pay for pH Test by using a Debit/Credit Card. When You initiate a payment transaction and/or issue a online payment Instruction and provide Your debit/credit Card details:

  * You warrant that You are fully and lawfully entitled to use such Debit/Credit Card for such transactions
  * You are responsible to ensure that the Debit/Credit Card details provided by You are accurate
  * You are authorizing the debit to the nominated Card account for the settlement of pH Test fees selected by you along with the applicable Fees.
  * You are responsible to ensure that sufficient credit is available on your nominated Card at the time of making the payment selected by You inclusive of the applicable Fee.

**Reach Us At:**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us by phone or mail, our contact information is as follows:

By Telephone : +91 7259 1047 94   
By email : query@elitmus.com   
OR Contact us at: 

**Address:  
eLitmus Evaluation Private Limited  
L-29, 2nd Floor, 2nd 'A' Main,  
6th sector, HSR Layout, Bangalore-560102 

Landmarks: Above State Bank of India, next to 'Fernhill Gardens' Apartments. 

**
